迷失前情提要
Previously on lost
我们会来接你
We will get you back there
抱歉  george
I'm sorry, george.
告诉我妹妹我爱她
Just tell my sister that I love her.
-你杀了naomi!  -她希望她的人来这里!
-you killed naomi! -she wants her people to come here.
相信我  等他们来时
And trust me, when they do,
我们离这越远越好
We had better be far away from here.
想活命就跟着我
if you want to live, you need to come with me
没人会跟着你的  John
no one's going anywhere with you, john.
-你在做什么  -跟以前一样  kate...
-what are you doing?  -same thing I've always done, kate--
活着
survivin'.
直升机声音越来越响了
The thunder's getting louder.
抱歉  ron
sorry, ron.
探测器在水下5000米除了海鲜什么也没发现
Drone's got nothing but seafood at 5,000 meters below.
你那里找到什么了吗
You picking anything up with yours?
零蛋  我想尽快去
Zip. I'm trying to get her a peek over this ridge
山脊上上看看
As soon as I can.
声纳发现了点东西
Sonar's pinging up something now.
你想切换信号吗
Hey, you wanna switch feeds?
收到  执行
roger that.
我正朝1-3-7方向探索
I'm headed on a bearing of about 1-3-7
从坐标上看我们超过了指定搜索区域
From the coordinates we pulled off our guy's map.
别太吃惊
But don't hold your breath.
磁强计在下面探测到了
Magnetometer is picking up
探测到了大量异常磁场
A hell of a lot of anomalies down here.
一箱金银财宝吗?
A chest full of doubloons?
做梦吧你
Keep dreaming, ron.
换到下一个山脊然后重新校准坐标
Let's swing around on the next bridge and recalibrate.
这...你看到了吗?
Uh... are you getting this?
什么?  什么东西
What? what's up?
是...  是架飞机
It's... it's an airplane.
我的天哪
oh, my god.
是大洋航空815号
It's oceanic 815.
这段奇怪的画面是从
This haunting footage comes to us
克利斯汀号传来的
From the"christiane i,"
这艘印度洋上的海上打捞船
A salvage vehicle in the indian ocean.
克利斯汀号用了超过两个月的时间
For more than two months,
在巴厘岛外的巽他海深处
It's been scouring the depths of the sunda trench off bali
寻找沉没的古贸易船残骸
In search of the remains of sunken trading ships.
就在昨晚
Late last night,
她的两艘远程遥控探测仪
Two remotely operated vehicles, or r.o.v.s.,
证实了
That verified what
国家交通运输安全委员会
The national transportation safety board
一直担心的
Had long feared, that the commercial aircraft...
你的蛋要怎么做  dan?
How you want your eggs, dan?
在2004年9月22日从澳大利亚的悉尼
Disappeared after departing sydney, australia,
起飞之后就消失了的客机
On september 22nd, 2004...
怎么了?  他们发现了那架消失的飞机了?
So what happened? they found that missing plane?
这段录象证实了大洋航空815
This footage confirms that oceanic flight 815...
-Dan?  -的确在海上坠毁了
Dan? did in fact crash at sea.
-Dan?  -在这悲痛的发现之后
Dan? even with this tragic discovery...
-Dan你这么伤心干嘛  -受害者的家属们表示
Dan, why are you so upset? victims families say
他们的悲痛还远未结束
That they're left without any sense of closure.
我不知道
i don't know.
-我找不到我的防弹背心  -找找座位下面
I can't find my vest! check under your seat!
-我找过了!  -准备好
-i already did!  -get ready!
把我的拿上
Here, just take mine!
所有人员跳出去!  立刻!
Everybody out! now!
-跳吧  天才  -不  不
-hey, genius! go!  -no, no!
快跳
go!
不!
声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：思思　多多　天龙　小帝
校对：奇奇  hailongren  小帝 许愿
字幕总监制：何何  梁良
你好
hey there.
你是jack?
are you jack?
对  我是jack
yeah, i'm jack.
你是谁?
who are you?
我是daniel faraday
I'm daniel faraday.
我是来这里救你们的
I'm here to rescue you.
嗨  dan
hey, dan.
那架直升机  你们来了多少人?
The chopper-- how many of you were on it?
包括我有4个
Uh, four, including me.
那其他人呢?
So what happened to the rest of them?
对  我也不清楚
Yeah, yeah, i, uh, have no idea.
我不知道他们有多少能在
I don't know how many of 'em were able to get out
飞机坠毁之前逃出来  我跳伞了  丢了我的...
Before it went down. I just-- I jumped, and I lost my, uh,
那啥  我的  我的包
What do you call it? my--my pack.
我的电话也在包里
My phone was in my pack.
-如果有电话的话就能...  -我们有电话
-if I had my phone，i would just, uh... -we have a phone.
你们有电话
You--you have a phone. uh...
谢了
Thank you. thanks.
Minkowski
minkowski.
-george吗  我是daniel  -Dan?
Hey, george. it's daniel. dan?
-是的  -直升机坠毁了  发生什么事了
Yeah. the chopper com went dead. what the hell happened up there?
是的  我也不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
George  是电磁风暴
George, there was-- there was an electrical storm.
所有的仪器都失灵了
All the instruments, they just-- I think they went down.
但是  我...
But listen, I made--i made contact
-我和一些幸存者取得了联系  我们...  -关掉扬声器行吗
-with some of the survivors, and, uh, we were just, uh-- -dan, am I on speaker?
能给我一分钟吗
Would you give me just--just one second?
-别担心  -我也不知道
Don't worry. I don't know...
Naomi替我们掩护了的
Naomi covered for us.
他们不知道locke把她怎么样了
They don't know what locke did to her.
你确定吗?
You sure about that?
好的  好的
okay, okay.
船还没有收到其他人的信息  但是...
So the boat hasn't heard from anybody else yet, but, uh,
这是G.p.s.异频雷达收发机
These are g.p.s. transponders,
我们队里所有的人都有这个
And my team and I are all wearing these.
收发机会把我们的位置发送到船上
The transponders will send the locations back to the ship,
然后船会把位置信号
And then the ship will send
再发回到手机上
All the locations back into the phones.
这...那是我的信号
Uh... oh, there is my signal right there,
希望我们能尽快收到
And hopefully, we'll get the signals
队里其他人的信号
From the rest of the team soon.
能帮我找到他们吗
Will you help me find 'em?
-当然  -好的
-absolutely.  -okay.
谢谢
thank you.
你们其他人在那
Hey, where are the rest of your people?
大部分都在海滩上
Most of them are back at the beach.
大部分?
most of them?
伙计  你是怎么了
Dude, what's wrong with you?
你会被雷击中的
You're gonna get struck by lightning.
风暴就快要过去了  Hugo
Storm's about to pass, hugo.
现在可是雨季  我们得...
It's a freakin' monsoon. we gotta...
走吧
let's go.
为什么朝东边走
Why you going east?
你不是说房子在南边吗
I thought you said the barracks were due south.
因为  james我们得先绕一下路
Because, james, we have to make a little detour first.
绕路去哪
detour to what?
我得去个小房子（cabin有客舱的意思）
There's a cabin I have to go to.
但是那客舱不是在那边吗
But the cabin was back that way.
hugo  你在说什么
What did you say, hugo?
我...
i, uh,
以为你在说飞机的客舱
Thought your were talking about the airplane cabin.
为什么我们要浪费时间去个破屋
Why are we wasting our time going to some shack anyway?
因为我们必须去
because we're supposed to.
对  就好象你必须扔一把刀
Right, like you were supposed to throw a knife
在naomi那个小妞的背上
Into that naomi chick's back?
你不妨说这是
You mind telling us who you're getting
库兹上校的命令?(现代启示录马龙·白兰度饰演的)
your orders from,  colonel kurtz?
我是从walt那里知道的
I got 'em from walt.
Jack还没有回来
Jack still isn't back?
有事吗?
anything?
没有  但这是个巨大的岛
No, but it's a big island.
货船可能会从另外一边靠岸
The freighter could be approaching from the other side.
说得对
That's the spirit.
Juliet你和那帮人一起生活过
Juliet, you lived amongst the others.
为什么ben会说
Why would ben say
来这里的人是想害我们?
The people coming here intend to do us harm?
因为他是个骗子  想吓我们
Because he's a liar and he's trying to scare us.
ben经常这样做
That's what ben does.
或者  来这里的人
Or because the people coming here
真的是想害我们
Intend to do us harm.
你们还有多少支枪
How many guns do you have left?
那是你们直升机上的吗
Hey. is that from your chopper?
是的  它是...
Yeah, yeah. that, uh, yeah, they...
我们坠落时为了减轻重量扔的包裹
Reduced the weight load when we started going down.
我猜这也是为什么我也被推了出来
Ha ha. I guess that's why they pushed me out.
这是干什么的?
What's this for?
我不是负责装备...
I'm not in charge of, uh, packing, so...
你没事吧?
Um... you're not, huh?
我们该...  继续前进
We should, uh... you wanna keep moving?
daniel  为什么你们带枪了
Hey, daniel, why did you bring the gun?
只是防身之用
Yeah... as a precaution.
防什么?
Precaution against what?
解救你和你的人...
Rescuing you and your people...
不能说是首要任务
Can't really say its our primary objective.
那什么是?
then what is?
是miles
it's miles.
是miles  快来
It's miles. come on.
你说你看到了walt是什么意思
What the hell do you mean you saw walt?
梦里吗
in a dream?
不是在梦里  的的确确是walt  只是...
No dream. it was walt. only...
要高一点
taller.
高一点?  像个巨人吗?
Taller? what, like a giant?
好吧  那walt到底跟你说了什么
Okay, what exactly did walt tell you?
他说我有工作得完成
He said I had work to do,
那就是得阻止这个女人naomi
That I had to stop this woman, naomi,
把她的其他人带到这里
from bringing the rest of her people here
你没问为什么吗
what, you didn't ask any follow-up questions?
Ben给了我一枪然后把我留那等死
Ben had shot me and left me for dead.
Walt救了我,所以我照着他的话去做
walt saved my life, So I pretty much took him at his word.
他给了你一枪  你却好好
He shot you, yet here you are,
在森林里活蹦乱跳
Fit as a fiddle, trompin' through the jungle.
子弹从一边打进去从另一边出来
The bullet went in one side, came out the other.
如果我这里还是肾的话我早死了
I'd probably be dead if I still had a kidney there.
还有其他的要问吗
anything else?
在下面
It's down there.
Miles!
hey, miles!
miles!
他死了吗
is he dead?
退后  帅哥
Back up, handsome.
Miles!
whoa, whoa, whoa! whoa, whoa! miles!
别冲动  他们是来帮我们的
Take it easy. it's okay. they're here to help us.
没事的miles  他们是来帮忙的
It's okay, miles. they're just trying to help.
离他远点儿!  把手放在我能看见的地方
Hey! back away from him! hands where I can see 'em!
Kate  没事的
Kate, it's all right. it's okay.
你是Kate!
you're kate!
能告诉我naomi在哪吗
You wanna tell me where naomi is?!
什么
what?
naomi...  那个你杀了的女人
Naomi-- the woman you killed!
她在哪
where is she?
Gardner女士?
ms. gardner?
我是miles straume  我们刚才通过电话
I'm miles straume. we spoke on the phone earlier.
请进
Oh. oh, please come in.
哪间房?
Which room is it?
在楼上  过道最里面
It's upstairs at the end of the hall.
先付钱  200美金  只收现金
I get paid in advance. $200, cash only.
-你在电话里是说100美元  -那是我兄弟在警察局
You told me $100 on the phone. that was before my buddy at the police station
告诉我你的孙子被杀之前的价格
Told me your grandson was murdered.
现在要200美元了
It's gonna be $200.
好吧
fine.
不管你听见什么
No matter what you hear,
都不要上楼来
don't come up.
你呆在这里对你祖母
You're not doing your grandmother any good
一点好处也没有
Staying here, man.
你带给她了很多的痛苦
You're causing her a lot of pain.
我...
i...
我想下楼并告诉她你已经离开了
I wanna go downstairs and tell her you've gone.
但是现在要我这样做的唯一条件
But the only way I'm gonna be able to do that
就是你告诉我它在哪里
Is if you tell me where it is.
那么它在哪里?
so where is it?
你可以走了
you can go now.
这奏效了吗?
did it work?
是的
yeah.
他已经安息了
He's at peace now.
给
here.
退给你点钱  优惠你一半价格
You get a refund, half off.
这没有我想象中那么难
Wasn't as tricky as I thought.
谢谢
thank you.
谢谢了
Miles  miles
miles. miles! hey, hey!
你干嘛啊?  你要做什么?
What are you doing? what are you doing?
-他们是好人  -那为什么Naomi发送那个代码?
These are good people. they why'd naomi use the damn code?
是的  你还记得她说的
Yeah, you remember when she said,
"告诉我妹妹我爱她"?  她根本就没有妹妹
"tell my sister I love her"? well, she doesn't have a sister.
那是当我们在
That's what we're supposed to say
被捉住并且有枪指着我们脑袋时候才说的
If we get captured and have a gun to our heads.
就好像现在  Jack就应该说
Like right now jack here would say,
"告诉我妹妹我爱她"  明白了吗?
"tell my sister I love her." you get it?!
-我们没有杀害你的朋友  -那带我去看她的尸体
We didn't kill your friend. then take me to her body.
-Miles  那Charlotte还有Frank呢?  -带我去见Naomi!
Miles, what about charlotte? what about frank? take me to naomi!
听着  Naomi已经死了  但不是我们干的
Listen, naomi was killed, but not by us.
是...  是个叫John Locke的男人干的
It was--it was a man by the name of john locke.
他现在已经不跟我们在一起了
He's not with us anymore.
Kate  认真点  如果要我再问一次的话...
kate, seriously, if I have to ask you again--
听着  就算我带你去看她的尸体
Look, even if I took you to her body,
-你还是不会知道发生了什么的  -我会知道的!
You wouldn't know what happened. I'll know!
现在带我过去
Now take me to her body.
alex
alex.
alex, hey.
-什么事?  -我要告诉你件事
What? something I need to tell you.
闭上你的嘴  Mr.Linus
Keep your mouth shut, mr. linus.
Karl  如果你要跟我女儿睡的话
Karl. now if you're gonna sleep with my daughter,
你还是叫我Ben比较好
I insist you call me ben.
放松点孩子  这个人就是想要激怒你
Easy kid. guy's just trying to get in your head.
去走走或干点别的吧
Go take a walk or somethin'.
你介意我问你个问题吗?  James
Mind if I ask you a question, james?
是的  我介意
yeah, i do.
你为什么会离开Kate?
Why'd you leave kate behind?
别多费口舌了  Yoda
You're wasting your time, yoda.
我知道这不太令人愉快  但是让我们面对它吧
I know it's not pleasant, but let's face it.
你现在真的没有机会了
You really don't stand a chance now.
什么机会?
chance at what?
James  看看你自己
James, look at yourself.
是的  在这个岛上
Yes, on this island,
你很勇敢大胆而且帅气
You're brave, daring, handsome.
你是个人物
you're someone.
但如果你带他们离开...
But if you left with them...
回到现实社会  你这样生活在社会底层的小混混
Back in the real world, a lowlife scam artist like you
根本竞争不过一流外科医生的
Could never compete with a first-class surgeon.
我觉得当你选择
I think kate was really upset
跟我们一起走  Kate很伤心
When you made your choice to come with us.
多亏了她还有Jack在身边抚慰她
Thank god she has jack there to comfort her--
james!
-不要  -不要干嘛?
Don't. don't what?!
-谁可以告诉我为什么要让这个人活着?
Anyone want to tell me why we're keeping this guy alive?!
我们让他活着
we're keeping him alive
是因为他在这个岛上比我们任何人时间都长
Because he's been on this island a lot longer than any of us,
因为他有我们想要的信息
Because he has information we need,
还有除了他的嘴巴
And because apart from his mouth,
他完全不会有危险
He's completely harmless.
他的嘴巴刺痛了你的心吗?
His mouth put that hole in your gut?
我们解决他吧  就这这里  就现在
Let's--let's execute him right here, right now,
在他女儿面前
In front of his daughter.
他对我们耍诡计只是时间问题  Johnny
It's only a matter of time before he gets us, johnny.
我打赌他已经想好了
And I'll bet he's already figured out
下一步怎么对付我们
How he's gonna do it.
所以  你来牵着他吧
So you walk him.
他在干嘛?
What is he doing?
这光线...
the light...
有些奇怪  不是吗?
Is strange out here, isn't it?
看起来...  看起来好像不是
It's... it's kind of like it doesn't--
分散的不太舒服
It doesn't scatter quite right.  dan? dan?
Dan?
你叫Dan  对吗?
Your name's dan, right?
听着  Dan
listen, dan,
我知道你不想任何人受到伤害  对吗?
I know that you don't want anybody to get hurt, right?
那你为什么不把那东西放在一边呢?
So why don't you just put that away?
因为  Miles...  会杀了我
Because, um, miles... would kill me?
但我们只是想帮帮忙
But we're just trying to help--
Kate  你在浪费时间
Kate, you're wasting your breath.
我们只需静观其变  然后看看会发生什么  好吗?
Let's just let this play out and see what happens, okay?
他们没有杀她
They didn't kill her.
他们说的是事实
It happened like they said it did.
是Charlotte
it's charlotte.
她就在离这里三公里的地方  好吧  我们去找她
She's only 3 kilometers from here. all right, then. let's go get her.
我说了  我们一起走
I said let's go.
-你应该把枪放下  -什么?
You need to put the guns down. what?!
-把枪放下  -我为什么要这么做?
Put the guns down. now why would I do that?
因为我的朋友们现在就躲在丛林里
Because our friends are out in the jungle right now
把枪对着你还有他的头
Holding a gun at your head and his head.
我会不计较刚刚的误会的
So I'm gonna forget about the misunderstanding.
-把枪放下  -你当我是白痴啊
Just put the guns down. come on. how stupid do you think i--
我不知道  Miles
I don't know, miles.
你有多傻
How stupid are you?
在你认为这是真实的之前
How many different languages do you have to read that in
你读过几个语言的版本了
Before you believe it's true?
那么出现过几种不同的语言呢?
How many different languages are there?
打扰一下
excusez-moi.
他想知道我们是不是迷路了  告诉他我们的工作
He wants to know if we're lost. remind him that people in our line of work
是很危险的  而且要保守秘密
Are terrible at keeping secrets.
我知道那个发掘工作的事
I know about the dig.
他说那个地方已经被关闭了
He says the site is closed.
那么告诉他打开它
Then tell him to open it.
恐龙?
dinosaur?
不是几百万年以前的
Not by a few million years.
这是北极熊
It's an ursus maritimus.
等等  "ursus"就是熊的意思?
Wait, "ursus" as in bear?
是北极熊的意思
As in polar bear.
Charlotte  我们在沙漠里  这是个骗局  不是吗?
Charlotte, we're in the desert. this is a hoax, right?
-她想知道你在用这个锤子干嘛  -在挖掘
He wants to know what you're doing with the hammer. excavating.
这是项圈吗?
Is that a collar?dan?
嗨
hi.
你也好
hi yourself.
我们在担心你什么时候回来
We were worried when you didn't get back,
于是我们回到座舱然后从哪里开始追踪你
So we went out to the cockpit and tracked you from there.
-谢谢了 但是很有帮助  -别再提了
Thanks for that, for what it's worth. don't mention it.
有人告诉我  calvary就在这里
Somebody could've told me that the calvary were here.
我给你了...
I gave you that...
一点提示
wink.
你们叫什么名字?
What are your names?
我叫Daniel Faraday  这位是Miles...
Uh, I'm daniel faraday, and this is miles--
别告诉他我姓什么
Don't tell him my last name.
我猜就单Miles
I guess this is just miles.
-你是做什么工作的  Daniel?  -我是个物理学家
What do you do for a living, daniel? I'm a physicist.
我的意思是  我想你可以叫我物理学家
I mean, I guess you could call me a physicist.
-我不喜欢被分到哪一类  -Dan  我向上帝保证
I don't really like being pigeonholed into one-- dan, I swear to god,
你再多说一句  我就把你手指弄断
You say one more word, I'm gonna break your fingers.
-那你是做什么的  Miles?  -我是收集土壤样本的
And what do you do, miles? I collect soil samples.
很不错  你可能可以帮我的忙
Well, that's nice. well, maybe you can help me.
你说  你不是营救队伍里的
You say you're not here on a rescue mission,
外面的世界都认为我们已经死了
And the world at large believes us to be dead.
但是我们在这里  活着而且还不错
But here we are, alive and well,
但你却没有对看见我们感到很奇怪
And you don't seem remotely surprised to see us.
天哪  你们是太平洋航空815号航班的幸存者!
Oh, my god. You guys were On oceanic flight 815. Wow!
想要这种效果是吧?
Is that better?
难以置信你们居然活下来了
I can't believe You're alive.
你们有多少人?
How many of you are there?
你问这个干吗?
Why do you wanna know?
我为什么不能问?
Why wouldn't i want to know?
48个活下来了
48 of us Survived the crash.
这不算尾舱的那些人
That's not counting The tail section.
-他们现在八成已经死了  -hugo
They're pretty much All dead now-- hugo.
你们这段时间一直住在这儿?
So you've all been living here This entire time?
那是你孩子吗?
Is that your baby?
是啊  她叫aaron
Yeah. This is aaron.
你在这岛上生的她吗?
Did you have him Here on the island? Mm-hmm.
真了不起
That's amazing.
我还有一大堆的问题
Well, i've got about A million more questions
想问你们
I want to ask you,
但是得先把你们带回渡轮
But they can wait until we Get you back to the freighter.
我们人手一个这种通信器
We've all got One of these transponders,
如果我们就在这呆着  他们马上就会来  好吧?
So if we just sit tight, they're Gonna be here soon, okay?
你们这个队伍...  一共几个人?
This team of yours-- How many of you are there?
算我4个
Four, including me.
你们的直升机怎么了?
And what happened To your helicopter?
不知道  驾驶员想降落
I don't know. The pilot Was trying to put it down.
降在哪里?
Where?
不知道  当时我不得不跳
I don't know. i had to jump.
情况一片混乱
It was chaos.
能活下来我觉得很幸运
I'm lucky to be alive.
起来  你跟我们走
Get up. You're coming with us.
什么?
What? What?
我们得留在这里他们才能找到
We need to stay where we are So that they can find us.
这就是问题所在  我们不想暴露
See, there's your problem. We don't want to be found.
我要是你的话肯定不会拿着那东西乱跑
I wouldn't mess around With that if i were you.
-试着播几个号码又没什么?  -有关系
It can't hurt To try and call someone else. Oh, it can hurt.
-你按了什么?  -什么都没碰
What'd you do? I didn't do anything.
你们的朋友charlotte
Your friend--charlotte.
她在移动
She's moving.
移动的很快
And she's moving fast.
她在逃脱什么
She's running from something.
据此显示  她就在这
according To this, she's right here.
charlotte?!
Charlotte?!
charlotte!
Charlotte!
在那里  在那里
Over there. Over there.
vincent
Vincent.
locke抓到她了
Locke's got her.
敬告观众朋友们下面即将出现的画面
we want to caution our viewers that the images
未经过处理
they are about to see are graphic in nature.
建议慎重观看
viewer discretion is advised.
有关部门公布了
authorities have released dramatic footage
太平洋航空815航班
of the sunken remains
海底的残骸
of oceanic flight 815.
国家运输安全委员会
the national transportation safety board
设立了一部求助热线
has set up a hotline
请遇难者家属及时拨打
for family members of the oceanic victims.
国家运输安全委员会已经开始
the n.t.s.b. Has begun
辨认死者身份
the victim identification process.
我们得知
we have confirmation
这位就是飞行员  seth norris上尉
that this is the pilot-- captain seth norris.
国家运输安全委员会在一份报告中说
in a statement, the n.t.s.b. Said that,
由于残骸所在的深度...
"due to the sheer depth of the..."
尸体...  很难被打捞
"...recovery of the bodies would be next to impossible.
我们只能希望
"we can only hope
死者身份鉴定能给
"that identification will provide closure
死者家属以慰藉
to the families of the victims."
国家运输安全委员会  太平洋热线
national transportationSafety board, oceanic hotline.
我找你们主管
Yeah, let me speak To your supervisor.
好的先生  您是死者家属吗?
Yes, sir. Are you a family Member of the deceased?
我不是  但我有空难相关信息
No, i'm not, but i got some Information on the crash.
能不能跟你们主管通话?
May i please speak To your supervisor?
-先生  能不能请您...  -我现在正盯着电视呢
Sirif you could just tell meLooki'm staring At the television right now.
你们在播放机身残骸的画面
You're broadcasting footage Of the wreckage
说那是飞行员  seth norris
And saying that That's the pilot, seth norris.
是啊  怎么了?
Yes, sir?
那不是他
Well, that's not him.
请等等
Please hold.
请问阁下是哪位?
who am i speaking with?
我是谁不重要  你们在播放
Doesn't matter who i am. You're showing footage
seth norris的画面  但那不是他
Of seth norris, And that's not him.
听着  这家伙19岁就跟他的高中小甜心结婚了
Listen, this guy married his High school sweetheart at 19.
他一直戴着他的结婚戒指的  告诉你
He always wore his wedding ring. And i'm telling you,
-那尸体手上没有戒指  -先生  很可能是坠机时...
There's no ring on that body.Sir, it's likely The ring fell off when--
告诉你  那不是他
I'm telling ya,That is not him.
那请问究竟
And how exactly is it
你有多了解norris上尉
That you know all about Captain norris?
因为那天本应是我驾驶开太平洋815航班的
Because i was supposed to be Flying oceanic 815 on that day.
是他们
That's them.
我的同队队员
That's somebody From my team.
你们干嘛?  我们来这都是为了你们
What's wrong with you people? We're here because of you.
我从直升机上跳下差点摔死
I just almost died Jumping out of a helicopter
就是因为你们给我们打了求救电话
Because you called us For help.
也许我们该去看看是谁发的信号
Maybe we should go see Who launched that flair.
-我是说  他们可能受伤了  john  -她在撒谎
Yeah, i mean,They could be hurt, john.She's lying.
而且无论如何他们来并不是为了我们
And whatever they came for,It isn't us.
-我们按原计划一直向前走  -是啊
We keep moving forward As planned.sure.
-谁叫你是那个跟高个儿walt的鬼魂谈话的人呢?
Who are we to argue With taller ghost walt? You know what?
-你们想干什么干什么  -我想让你跟着我们
You people Do whatever you want. I want you to come with us.
我不是在求你们同意
I'm not asking for permission.
如果你觉得你们能拦住我不去...
And if you think you're gonna bloody stop me From getting to my--
你干什么  狗娘养的!
what did you do, You son of a bitch?! Uhh!
防弹衣
Vest.
什么?
What?
防弹衣  防弹衣
Vest. Vest.
他还活着吗？
is he alive?
还有脉搏
he's got a pulse.
frank?  frank
Frank? Frank.
嘿  嘿  frank
Hey, hey. Frank.
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
出什么事了?
What happened?
我们被闪电击中了
We got struck by lightning.
frank  charlotte呢?
Frank, where's charlotte?
她在坠机前跳伞了
She bailed out just b-before We went down.
不知道她在哪儿  直升机在哪?
I don't know where she is. Where's the chopper?
我看到一头奶牛
I saw a cow.
Hey. Hey.
lapidus  直升机呢?  坠毁在哪儿了?
Lapidus, where's the chopper? Where did it crash?
坠毁?  你当我是菜鸟?
Crash? The hell kind of pilot You think i am?
我把她停在那了  完好无损
I put her down safe and sound Right over there.
这就是队员们?
so this is the team?
-你看过他们的资料了?  -是啊  真遗憾
you've familiarized Yourself with their profiles? Unfortunately, yes.
客气的说
With respect,
这些人不适合这种任务
These are the wrong people For a mission like this.
都没有野外生存的经验
None of them have Field experience,
没有参加过军事训练
Military training.
你不能就把他们往那里一扔
You can't just Drop them in unprotected.
-会很糟糕的  -他们并非没有受到保护  他们有你
It'll be a disaster. They're not unprotected. They have you.
我能做多少呢
there's only So much i can do.
你的谦逊就是最有用的
Your modesty Is positively charming.
这个任务十分机密  风险也大
This is a high-risk covert op In unstable territory.
没人监管会非常危险
It's dodgy enough Without having to babysit
一个疯子  一个驱鬼者  一个人类学家和一个酒鬼
A head case, ghostbuster, Anthropologist and a drunk.
公平的说  他也是个优秀的飞行员
To be fair, he's also A pretty good pilot.
这太疯狂了  要是我们找到815航班的幸存者怎么办?
It's madness. What if We find survivors from 815?
没有幸存者
There were no survivors.
是的  我知道  但是如果有呢?
Yes, i know. But what if There are survivors?
没有太平洋航空815航班的幸存者
There were nosurvivors Of oceanic 815.
别问问题  做你该做的
Don't ask questions. Just do What you were hired for.
这个队里的每个成员
Every member of this team
都是精挑细选的
Was selected For a specific purpose.
都得靠你了
Everything relies on you
把他们带过去  也要带回来
Getting them in,Getting them out
别让他们中的任何人死掉
And preventing anyone From getting killed.
能做到吗?
Think you can do that?
能
Sure.
怎么不能?
Why not?
有点小损伤
There's some minor damage,
整个机械系统还是完整的
But the mechanical systems Are intact.
就是说它还能飞?
So it'll fly, then?
肯定
Absolutely.
我现在能用电话吗?
Can i have the phone now?
跟你直说了  告诉我你们来这里干什么
Tell you what.I'll give you the phone
我就给你电话
If you tell me what You people are doing here.
你把电话给我 我就告诉你我们来这里干什么
I'll tell you. What we're doing here If you give me the phone.
别提你姐姐的事
Don't say anything About your sister.
喂?
Hello?
ragina  我是miles  我找minkowski
Regina, it's miles.I need to talk to minkowski.
minkowski现在接不了
Minkowski can't Come to the phone right now.
事关重大  去叫他
It's important. Go get him.
miles  他现在接不了
Miles, he can't Come to the phone right now.
好吧  叫他方便时打给我
All right, Have him call me when he can.
我得挂了
I gotta go.
你们干什么?
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What are you doing with her?
我们带她一起走
We're taking her with us.
为什么?  那不是naomi  一堆肉而已
What's the point? That's--that's Not naomi. It's just meat.
mils  我们不能把她丢在这里
Miles, we can't just Leave her here.
miles说的对  躲避那该死的风暴
Miles is right. We burned up Most of the damn fuel
把燃料都耗光了
Flying around in that storm.
我们要回到渡轮那里已经很勉强
We barely got enough To get back to the freighter.
所以不带任何多余的东西
We're not gonna carry Any unnecessary weight.
第二趟我肯定带上她  我答应你  dan
I'll take her on the next run.I promise, dan.
我那边背包里有条毯子
there's a blanketOver there by my backpack.
-能不能去拿来?  -好的
Would you grab it?Yeah.
看起来跟感觉一样糟糕吧?
Look as bad as it feels?
感觉怎样?
How bad does it feel?
你叫什么来着?
What's your name again?
Juliet
Juliet.
全名呢？
Juliet what?
Juliet burke
juliet burke.
Juliet burke...
你不在那架飞机上  对吧？
You weren't on that plane,were ya?
Miles！
Miles!
什么事？
Yeah?
这位是Juliet
This is juliet,
她不在飞机上
And she was not on the plane.
啊？你确定？
What?! you sure?
那该死的旅客名单都快被我翻烂了
You know how many times I studied that damn manifest?
相信我  飞机上没有叫Juliet burke的
Believe me,there's no "juliet burke" on that plane.
她是岛上居民
She's a native.
真的吗？
Really?
-他在哪？！ -离她远点！
Where is he?! back off!
-你问谁？ -想知道我们为什么在这儿？
Where's who? you wanted to know why we're here?
让我告诉你我们为什么在这儿
I'll tell you why we're here.
为了找Benjamin linus
We're here for benjamin linus.
现在快说他在哪？
Now where is he?
James  听我说
James,listen to me.
求你了  -闭上你的嘴
Please-- keep your mouth shut.
-你还好吧  -我觉得胸口压着块渣煤砖
You okay? I feel like I've got a cinder block on my chest,
-但没什么大碍  -对于你中枪我很抱歉
But I'll survive. I'm sorry you got shot.
我没想到会这样  -是吗？
I didn't intend for that to happen. really?
好像是你要朝我开枪的
Cause it seemed like you were about to shoot me yourself.
你死了对我有什么好？
What good would you be to me dead?
恩  我觉得现在好多了  谢谢
Well,I feel much more comfortable now. thanks.
我觉得现在
I guess this is the part
是说“我警告过你”的时候了
Where I'm supposed to say,"i told ya so."
James  我认错
James,I stand corrected.
你想让我开枪吗？
You want me to do it?
不  这是我的事
No,it's my mess.
我会了结的
I'll clean it up.
不  等等！
No,wait!
Danielle  护送alex离开这儿
Danielle,you should escort alex away from here.
Alex  我们走  快走  Alex  -不  不
Alex,come on,let's go. come on. alex. no! no!
她说的对  我们走吧
She's right. let's go.
不想看见他被杀的现在最好离开这儿
Anyone who doesn't want to see this should leave now.
拜托  john  我们应该谈谈这事!
Please. john,we should talk about this!
Claire  如果是你或者你的孩子中枪你会怎么做？
Claire,what if one of those bullets had hit you or the baby?
John 听着
john, Listen.
我有你要的消息
I have information that you need.
我知道答案
I have answers.
那怪物是什么？
What is the monster?
啊？
What?
那黑烟  那妖怪
The black smoke,the monster.
到底是什么?
What is it?
我不知道
I don't know.
再见吧  Benjamin
Good-bye,benjamin.
她叫Charlotte lewis
Her name is charlotte lewis.
Charlotte staples lewis
Charlotte staples lewis.
1970年7月2日在英国的艾塞克斯出生
Born july 2nd,1979,essex,england.
父母是david和jeanette
Parents--david and jeanette.
是三姐妹中最大的一个
Eldest of three,all girls.
她在bromsgrove长大
She was raised in bromsgrove,
在肯特郡上大学
Did her undergraduate studies at kent,
在牛津拿到文化人类学的博士学位
Took her phd in cultural anthropology at oxford.
另两位队员及一名飞行员同她一伙
She's here with two other team members and a pilot.
他们的名字是--daniel faraday
Their names--daniel faraday,
Miles straume
Miles straume,
Frank lapidus
Frank lapidus.
你的直觉是对的  john
Your instinct was right,john.
这些人是个威胁  而且如果你开枪
These people are a threat,and if you shoot me,
你就不会知道他们有多危险
You'll never know how great a threat they were,
因为我才知道他们在这里干嘛
Because I know what they're doing here.
我知道他们想要什么
I know what they want.
他们想要什么？
What do they want?
我  james  他们想要我
Me,james. they want me.
你怎么知道这些？
How do you know all this?
因为我有人在他们船上
Because I have a man on their boat.